So why is it important to warm up, to have warm up postures, warm up movements, before the regular yoga postures, the Asana?
It's important because of a number of things.
You want to warm up your muscles a bit, before you come in to a full-blown posture.
You want to move the spine in the six directions that it's capable of moving, so that you can warm up those movements, and get your body ready.
The muscles, the bones, getting them ready for the actual postures.
It's a good idea to practice six movements of the spine.
We're going to go over that.
It also helps you, doing warm ups also helps you, to notice your edge.
You can find out in an easy way where the edge for you is in each movement of the spine.
So it's really important to make sure, that before you come into the rest of your practice, you've practiced some warm up movements.